athleticalley.com 2012-03-12

# Privacy Policy | Athletic Alley

#### Information Collection

We care about our visitors, and you can feel safe giving us your information. We are the sole owner of the information collected from this website, AthleticAlley.com. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in our privacy policy below.  
Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor’s hard drive containing information about the visitor. We do not use cookies but links to our advertisers and other websites may use cookies to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. We do not control the use of cookies or technology used by third parties or the resulting information, and consequently we are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

#### Log Files

We keep simple log files to track what pages visitors have viewed and what links they have clicked on. In no way do these log files capture your personal identification or information.

#### Sharing

We do not share any of your personal information with advertisers, merchants, or any other third party.

#### Links

We are not responsible for privacy policies of other third parties such as advertisers and partner websites linking to or from AthleticAlley.com. Please read the privacy policies of those third parties for information on how they use any personal information you provide them. Our privacy statement applies solely to AthleticAlley.com. We are not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties.

#### Contests

At times we may conduct contests for our visitor’s. Visitor participation for these contests is voluntary, and in no way requires the visitor to give out personal information when choosing not to enter in the contest. Collected information may include contact information and demographic information, such as name, e-mail, address, state, etc. This information will only be used to notify the winners and award prizes.

#### Newsletter

If you subscribe to our newsletter, you can elect to unsubscribe at any time. Information stored in our database is not shared or sold to any third party. Subscribers wishing to unsubscribe to our newsletter can do so at anytime by using the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of each newsletter.

#### Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

#### Contacting Us

You may [Contact Us](http://www.athleticalley.com/contact/ "Submit Your Question or Comment") at anytime with questions about this policy or anything else.
